

Explore my work

www.staceyjenkins.co.uk

Send me an email

hello@staceyjenkins.co.uk

I'm a Welsh full-stack designer and illustrator who loves helping people leap ahead. I love creating fantastic content for fantastic people, from pencil to pixel and pride myself on making great things that do great things for the people I work with.

I never sweat the small stuff - every element from image, type and even sound and music, is paramount. But if I'm not pushing pencils or pixels, I'm playing D&D or writing adventures under the alias froginajar.

How can I help?

Considerable experience at logo design, print design, illustration and web design with Photoshop, Illustrator and Indesign.

Considerable experience with front-end web development with CSS, CSS3, jQuery, JS, RequireJS, HTML, HTML5, Jade/Pug, Bourbon Neat, Sass, SCSS, Susy and Compass (through Codekit), Github and Wordpress. Also considerable experience in prototyping with Invision and intermediate experience with Tumblr theming and email development.

Intermediate experience with motion graphics and video editing with After Effects CS6, Adobe Premiere and Final Cut Pro.

Employment

2016 MMP GLOBAL

Digital Designer

Digital designer and artworker working on site to create and amend existing brochures, letters, emails and marketing collateral for RAC. Pitched various technological improvements to improve workflows and created and coded HTML emails.

2013-2016 SCREAMING FROG LTD, HENLEY-ON-THAMES Senior Digital Designer

Collaborated with a small team of SEO consultants to produce promotional infographics, editorial imagery, illustrations and interactive mini website content for the agency's wide range of clients, including MOO and Which?. Also managed the agency's brand visuals. Frequently engaged and negotiated with client and consultant design requests as well as initiating design processes which are now standard within the company.

2011-2012 RM EDUCATION, ABINGDON

Multimedia Designer

Delivered visual concepts for RM Education's products and services, including nationwide print material (flyers, posters, wall planners, print advertisements and product factsheets) and online material (websites, animations, online shop pages, questionnaires, web banners and interactives.) Also corrected errors in existing online content and collaborated with fellow staff members with the creation of new online content. Also led a logo design workshop for Year 11 students.

Education

2006-2009 UNIVERSITY OF WALES

INSTITUTE, CARDIFF (UWIC)

BA(Hons) Graphic Communication (2:1)

2005-2006 SWANSEA INSTITUTE OF HIGHER EDUCATION (SIHE)

Foundation in Art and Design, specialising

in graphic communication (Merit)

2003-2005 GORSEINON TERTIARY COLLEGE

4 A Levels: English Language [A]
Graphic Design [A], Computing [B] and

Media Studies [B]